Alexis Y Sanabria

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Web Developer able to build a sophisticated web application with a full database backend all the way from mockup to rollout. Adept at working with diverse teams to implement projects. Also experienced in all project phases using Agile Methodologies. Extremely punctual, responsible, reliable, hard worker, quick learner and very well organized.

EXPERIENCE

Isara (Through Aerotek/AcTalent) - (Full stack Developer Remote) Waterloo, ON Mar 2021 - Nov 2021

- Collaborated to the Advance Project by coding, debugging, and testing the back-end and front-end, within a team of 30 other developers/testers.
- Provided code reviews to other team members branches before merging them with the base code.

AYP Web Creations - (Full stack Developer Freelancer) Cambridge, ON Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

• Designed and developed web applications/SaaS from scratch to deployment.

Amazing Pet Grooming - (Graphic Designer / Web Developer) Milton, ON 2016 - 2020

- Designed and developed compelling logos, flyers, and additional marketing materials.
- Designed a Full-stack-app to improve the way of handling clients and employees schedule
- Solved customer issues / IT related issues on a daily basis.

PRIVATE PROJECT COLLABORATION

Isara Advance Crypto Agility Suite Cryptographic management platform https://www.isara.com/products/isara-advance-crypto-agility-suite.html Enterprise solution for managing, discovering, and remediating cryptographic infrastructures within organizations.

BUILT PROJECTS

My Pet Grooming App Software as a Service (SaaS) https://www.mypetgroomingapp.com/

This SaaS, provides a simple way for small businesses to manage their clients (humans, pets, and services), their appointments (including online booking and clients-personal-profile), and their employees (virtual punch clock), as well as detailed reports on employees working hours, commissions earned, etc. Users can choose among different membership packages to subscribe either monthly or yearly. It was built using Javascript, ReactJs (Class and Functional components), HTML, CSS, Context API, Apollo Client, MailGun, Bootstrap NodeJs, Express, PassportJs, JWT, MySql, Sequelize, GraphQL.

Pet Grooming Web Application Full Management System for a Small business. https://www.amazingpetgrooming.ca/

This React Application was built for a Pet Grooming business. The admin of the page is able to add employees into the system, so they can login to the private pages based on their roles, where they can manage the clients' database, add appointments to their own Calendars and adjust their working hours. Customers are also able to book appointments online. This Application solved several issues this business faced in the past.

Cambridge, ON N1T-1J8 905-299-2366

alexisyep@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://www.alexisysanabria.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexis-sanabria-80002574/

Github:

https://github.com/alexisvepes

SKILLS

FRONT-END **BACK-END** React Node **Express Typescript** MySQL Redux PostgreSQL **Javascript** MongoDB HTML CSS/SASS GraphQL **CSS Modules** NodeMailer Bootstrap **Iwt Authentication** Passport Is

JQuery Handlebars

Rest API Apollo Client Firebase

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

React Native

OTHER TECHNOLOGIES / SKILLS

VS Code GitHub / GitLab Git Version Control Git Bash MVC Pattern

Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects Bilingual: Spanish/English

EDUCATION

University of Toronto, Toronto, ON Full-stack Web Development Bootcamp 2018-2019

An intensive 6-month long bootcamp, dedicated to designing and building full stack web applications.

Computer Programming Program 2002-2003

1 year program dedicated to computer programming fundamentals using Visual Basic, as well as computer maintenance, and graphic design: Photoshop/Illustrator.